[Music]
hello everyone and welcome to the
cottage fairy
in this video i wanted to share how i
resolved many of my inner struggles
by getting back in touch with my
childhood spirit
for those of you who don't know i work
with children for a living
and i'm constantly surprised by their
frankness curiosity
joy and insight into the human condition
just the other day i was told by a
little boy that more than anything in
the world
he wanted to be a star in the night sky
so that people may wish on him
i found this to be a clever idea and
decided to make a painting
inspired by the night sky through the
eyes of a dreaming child
i was able to transform my experience of
daily living
by reigniting my imagination and
childlike joy
have you tried jumping in rain puddles
recently finding little innocent joys
like that
helped me recall the wonder and magic
and beauty
of daily living
[Music]
creating meaningful human connection can
sometimes feel
complex and sadly to some unattainable
but as young children there was a time
when we were unencumbered by feelings of
inadequacy
and self-judgment we simply reached out
with openness
and directness unafraid of what was to
come
i think there is much wisdom to be
learned from the hearts of children
and many broken spirits healed simply by
recalling a time before
painful experiences stole their ability
to love without fear
[Music]
as a child i was enchanted by the forest
beside my home
and i'd often take little pieces of it
back with me
in the form of pinecones feathers and
abandoned birds nests
i'd like to imagine they were little
gifts left for me by the fairies
even today i find that one's environment
is key to their ability to thrive
this may not be true for everyone but
for me it was vital to create a space
in which i felt i could be my best self
[Music]
in order to get back in touch with
myself i
pursued the interest that i'd always had
as a child and now still
these are things that are intrinsic to
who you are
to me that was my love of nature of art
of reading by keeping alive passions
that you have had for your entire life
i find you consequently connect with
your inner soul
[Music]
do
so
[Music]
the greatest challenge in my life is one
that i think that many of us face
especially if you have a more sensitive
spirit
it is to be unashamed there was a time
when you had no concept of shame
when you were very young you had never
felt it before
your past does not define you and your
future is unwritten
new beginnings never come too late and
all you can do
is go forward and to be proud of who you
are
[Music]
i hope you found this video comforting i
would love to hear about your favorite
childhood memories below hope you have a
lovely
day or night and i will see you next
week